[
  {


    "type": "BasicCard",
    "front": "Who is the first African American President?",
    "back": "Barack Obama"
  },
  {

    "type": "BasicCard",
    "front": "When did we start this course?",
    "back": "Feburary 2nd"
  },
  {
    "type": "BasicCard",
    "front": "Who is the most basic player in the NBA as of 2017?",
    "back": "Kwhai Lenoard"

  },
  {
    "type": "BasicCard",
    "front": "Who was the man of peace?",
    "back": "Ghandi"

  },
  {
    "type":"BasicCard",
    "front": "What company has great company culture?",
    "back": "Patagonia"

  },
  {
    "type": "BasicCard",
    "front": "What can you do to always get what you want?",
    "back": "Smile"
  },
  {
    "type":"BasicCard",
    "front":"Why did Trump become President?",
    "back": "Mindless individuals"
  },
  {
    "type":"BasicCard",
    "front":"Why did the NFL cut down on hits to the head?",
    "back": "Concussions"
  },
  {
    "type": "ClozeCard",
    "front": "How many teams are there in the NFL?",
    "back": "33"
  },
  {
    "type": "ClozeCard",
    "front": "What's the most points scored in a NBA game?",
    "back": "81",
  },
  {
    "type": "ClozeCard",
    "front": "If you eat a lot of carrots does your vision get better?",
    "back": "No,that was a myth that was developed over one of the World Wars"
  },
  {
    "type": "ClozeCard",
    "front": "Can white men jump?",
    "back": "Come on now......NO"
  }
  
]
